Amrita Neekhara

https://www.linkedin.com/in/amrita-neekhara-ba8326152/

Summary

Quality analyst having 5 years experience, with attention to details, helping build quality products in the field of artificial intelligence and robotic process automation. Working directly with business team to improve user experience for digital assistant.

EDUCATION

Shri Ram Institute of Technology

Jabalpur, Madhya Pradesh

Email: amrita.neekharal@gmail.com

Mobile: +91-8160584657

B.Tech. in Computer Science; Percentage: 72%

Jul 2009 - June 2013

St. Thomas Higher Secondary School

Intermediate Education (10+2); Percentage: 61.23%

Maihar, Madhya Pradesh

Jul 2007 - June 2009

EXPERIENCE

Simplifai.ai

Pune, India

Quality Analyst

Nov 2018 -Present

- **Quality Assurance**: Debug complex application through the use of systematic tests to develop, apply and maintain quality standards. Perform analysis of results to ensure functionality and recommend corrective action.
- **User Experience Design**: Contribute to the design of useful, usable, and desirable user interfaces in a team environment for Digital Assistant widget and application.
- **Agile Team Planning**: Review progress and assign tasks to facilitate agile development using VSTS. Demo the application to managers and AI trainers for Digital Assistant(Chatbot).

Velocis systems Pvt. Ltd

Gandhinagar, India

Contract Software Developer (National Informatics Centre India)

June 2016 - Oct 2018

- **Testing**: Prepare test plan and summary report documents. Coordinate with team for the encountered issues and their resolutions. Provide knowledge transfer to team members and managers with involved and new features being introduced.
- **Development**: Responsible for task Analysis, allocation and delivery on time. Creation of relevant documents, reports, presentations over different modules of the application.

NTT Data Global Delivery Services Pvt. Ltd.

Gurugram, India

Junior Executive

May 2015 - Feb 2016

• **Responsibilities**: Reading, understanding and maintaining specifications and technical references specific to module. Prepare summary report documents. Configure the application (End to end for solution) specific to the Clients requirement.

Projects

Digital Assistant - CHATBOT

Nov 2018 - Present

Test Components: Front-End, API, Chat Widget

Simplifai.ai

- Digital Assitant application allows users to create a chatbot by providing conversation training examples and response flow for Norwegian and English Language.
- Create, update & execute test plans for quality assurance and provide result visibility to team.
- Localization testing to ensure compatibility for Norwegian and English language on web application.
- Testing for response flow and licenses in multibot and chatbot enviornment. Build chatbot from scratach as alpha user and test responses in widget as setup on admin panel.
- API testing to verify integrity of application with NLU and Backend system.
- Smoke and Sanity testing during to provide approval for production deployment.
- Collect review from AI trainers and discuss with product manager to improve overall product.

Digital Assistant - EMAILBOT

July 2019 - Present

Test Components: Front-End, Email-bot

Simplifai.ai

- Digital Assistant application allows users to create a email-bot by fetching the emails and bot will automatically categorized emails with entities and category.
- Create, update & execute test plans for quality assurance and provide result visibility to team.
- Localization testing to ensure compatibility for Norwegian and English language on web application.
- Build email-bot from scratch as alpha user and test responses in email-bot as setup on admin panel.
- Testing to verify integrity of application with NLU and Backend system.
- Smoke and Sanity testing during to provide approval for production deployment.
- Collect review from AI trainers and discuss with product manager to improve overall product.
- Perform E2E testing.
- Create reports for stakeholders using VSTS

Identity Server

Nov 2018 - Present

Test Components: SSO, Front-End, Database

Simplifai.ai

- Identity server is single sign authentication application for licensing and role assignment handling in various products of Simplifai.
- Create and update testing plans for Single sign authentication application using VSTS.

Claimslink Automation

Jan 2019 - May 2019

Test Components: RPA, MailBox, APIs, CRM, Sharepoint

Simplifai.ai

- Claimslink automation provides a way to extract information from outlook mails in Norwegian Language and assign categories with help of attachment & information extracted from mail text. After assignment documents gets uploaded to sharepoint and information to CRM for case creation & updation.
- Connect with various teams to understand the test coverage and scope of each component.
- · Create data of expected output for mails and document attachments from shared data.
- Used UIPath for testing RPA Bot along with outlook emails. Verify results in logs and Outlook folders.
- Test NLU apis for Email classification, document categorization & entity extraction using swagger.
- Reported various bugs related to performance & exceptions which helped in building robust process.

Human Resource Management System

June 2017 - Co 2017

Technology Used: VB.net, SQLServer

National Informatics Centre

- HRMS is portal for contractual employees under National health mission for payroll & attendance.
- Worked solely for development, testing and demo of application.
- Gather requirements during meething with NHM officers and develop application in accordance.

Gujarat Livelihood Promotion

June 2016 - June 2017

Technology Used: VB.net, SQLServer

National Informatics Centre

- The objective of this Special Project for Skill Development is to ensure a time-bound training and capacity building program for bringing specific number of Below Poverty Line (BPL) families above the poverty line through placement ensuring regular wage employment.
- Worked as a Primary user for the live support event at the client location. Interact with client to gather requirement and prepare Data Collection Workbooks. Coordinate with team for requirement analysis.

Personal Project

Healthy Girl Mar 2019 - Apr 2019

Technology Used: Google Action, Dialogflow

- Designed conversational bot which can be accessed using Google assistant on any compatible device.
- Deployed bot successfully with suggestion chips and closed conversation flow.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages:Python, VB.netDatabase:SQLServerMethdologies:Agile, WaterfallReporting Tools:VSTS, JIRA

Testing Methods: Blackbox, Smoke, Sanity, Regression, Functional Testing, API Testing, RPA Bot Testing, E2E

Testing

CERTIFICATE, COMPETITIONS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Received prize from Google for deploying conversational bot "Healthy Girl" on Google Assistant. (Ok google talk to Healthy Girl).
- Demo of HRMS portal to Principal Secretary, Health & Family Welfare Department, Government of Gujarat, India.
- Certified in Manual testing from Unicode technologies, Ahmedabad.

•